[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many orders of trilobite are there?", "correct_answer": "10", "incorrect_answers": ["9", "3", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1994 movie is this quote from: My them. Every paranoid schizophrenic has one; a them, a they, an it. And you want to hear about my them, dont you??", "correct_answer": "In the Mouth of Madness", "incorrect_answers": ["Dead Alive", "The Dark Half", "Event Horizon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Ernest Borgnine is a mason.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the senator who attempts to extort money from Michael in The Godfather Part II?", "correct_answer": "Geary", "incorrect_answers": ["Stockton", "McAllister", "Ellis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Having in mind the demand and supply laws, what will happen to the equilibrium of price and quantity of automobiles if wages of workers manufacturing them increase?", "correct_answer": "Price will increase; quantity will decrease.", "incorrect_answers": ["Price will decrease; quantity will increase.", "Price will increase; quantity will increase", "Price will decrease; quantity will decrease"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Andie Walsh", "correct_answer": "Pretty in Pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Class Reunion", "Some Kind of Wonderful", "Weird Science"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the butler in The Aristocats?", "correct_answer": "Edgar", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeeves", "Andrew", "Albert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1980 movie contains the following quote: I understand you lost your wife and daughter a little while ago. Maybe it shook you up. Maybe too much... *Maybe*, you need help.?", "correct_answer": "The Changeling", "incorrect_answers": ["Poltergeist", "The Amityville Horror", "The Watcher in the Woods"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kathmandu is the capital city of what country?", "correct_answer": "Nepal", "incorrect_answers": ["Gabon", "Togo", "Rwanda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The growth hormone is released from this gland.", "correct_answer": "Hypophysis", "incorrect_answers": ["Pancreas", "Adrenal Gland", "Pineal Gland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Julies parents owned a Pizza Hut in the movie Valley Girl.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following fats contain trans-fats?", "correct_answer": "Partially hydrogenated fats", "incorrect_answers": ["All types of animal fats", "None of these", "Non-hydrogenated fats"]}]